Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
EPISODE 9
Your hand
is warm.
Were your hands cold?
No.
Is it much warmer now?
You know...
I've been dying to hold this hand
but I held back...
to avoid crossing the line
between a CEO and an employee.
So take responsibility for this.
Take responsibility?
No matter how hard things get
don't let go of my hand.
Okay.
But then
things are already chaotic at work.
If people find out
that we're seeing each other...
I know.
We'll keep it a secret at work.
For now
let's focus
on getting to know each other.
Thank you for understanding.
Oh, right.
Bundle up. It's freezing out.
Hurry home. I'll head inside too.
I'll wait until you go in.
Come on.
It's too cold. Please hurry and go.
After you.
Fine, I'll get going.
Go.
I will.
Why are you still standing there?
You should go.
Okay, I'll get going now.
This is crazy.
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
Good night. See you tomorrow.
Sweet dreams.
Sweet dreams to you too.
MS. NAM DA-REUM
APPELLO
KNOT
You've got this, Da-reum.
Hello.
Good morning.
Well, look who's here.
Da-reum!
Da-reum, you're back.
Hello.
I'm officially back to work.
Da-reum, I've missed you!
- Me too.
- Seriously.
Da-reum.
It's so nice to have
the three of us back together.
Hey, Da-reum! Welcome to Appello!
Remember, sweetie?
I blocked the camera for you.
- Thank you so much.
- Don't mention it.
- You really did that?
- Yes, of course.
- Are you serious?
- Dead serious.
Oh, right.
Sweetie, what about your resignation?
It was rejected because she skipped
the electronic approval process.
She didn't request to work remotely,
so it's an unexcused absence.
I'll make sure
to follow the protocol from now on.
Oh, and I'll put in overtime
to make up for the time I missed.
Jeez.
Well...
Please stick to the protocol.
Get back to work.
- Yes, sir.
- Yes, Mr. Kang.
- Protocol...
- Welcome back.
- Congrats.
Protocol.
- This is such a relief.
- Oh, right.
Mr. Kang may sound harsh
but he was actually
so worried about you.
Did you make it to work okay?
Meet me in the storage.
- Hello.
Found it.
Where is he?
Did you get a good night's sleep?
Yes.
Relax. There's nobody around.
What if someone sees us?
I just wanted to talk.
This isn't going to work.
We need to set some rules.
Rules?
Secret office romance rules.
Rule one. No touching at work.
1. NO TOUCHING AT WORK
And definitely no standing close
when people are around.
- Rule two.
- Let's start the meeting.
- Yes, sir.
ROMANTIC NIGHT-VIEW SPOTS IN SEOUL
SEOUL NIGHT DATE IDEAS
Don't make it obvious
that you're dating.
2. DON'T MAKE IT OBVIOUS
THAT YOU'RE DATING
ROMANTIC NIGHT-VIEW SPOTS IN SEOUL
We have to be careful
to avoid any office gossip.
Be extra careful, okay?
Rule three.
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
I miss it.
What exactly do you mean?
APPELLO STAFF NOTICE CHAT
I MISS IT
I meant next year's business plan.
Personal messages should only be sent
through text.
Wait, no. We might mix up
the chat rooms
so no texting at work at all.
3. NO TEXTING AT WORK
And if you keep
startling me like this
you'll get a demerit.
- A demerit?
- Yes.
If they pile up
you have to buy food and coffee.
I won't even make
eye contact with you at work.
Wait. That's a bit harsh,
don't you think?
So be careful.
This feels unfair.
Shouldn't there be a reward too?
No, this is...
This is how it normally works.
I'm the only one getting demerits.
She could just give me a warning.
So unfair...
This is an exception.
An exception?
Thank you.
Da-reum, Ms. Kim needs the sample
urgently. Have you found it?
What?
- Yes, I'm bringing it now.
- Okay.
Go on.
Still, I got a kiss.
She gave me a kiss.
MASTER IM CHEONG-RIM
AND ARTIST LEE CHAN
KNOT KEYCHAIN DIY STATION
UNFRAMED: KNOTTING
UNTYING TRADITIONS TO TIE IT ANEW
Da-reum!
Oh, hello!
It's much better than I imagined.
Master Im.
It must've been hard
setting it all up.
Not at all. I actually had
a lot of fun preparing it.
She said she would've canceled
if you hadn't followed through.
Oh, stop it.
You must've read the article.
Yes, I did.
But I don't care what others say.
I know your work ethic.
Thank you, ma'am.
All right, what should I do?
You'll do a quick rehearsal
with Director Lee Chan later.
With Director Lee Chan?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
- Shall we go this way?
- Sure.
Hello, sir.
Hello.
Have you been well?
Yes.
Director Lee.
Can I talk to you briefly
after the event?
THE KNOT
Loop it through like this
and it all takes shape.
Now, that's your first knot.
What I'm making is
called Dongsimgyeol.
It means a knot of one heart.
If you gently pull this end...
Wait, it's uneven.
It came loose. Give me a second.
See?
Pull too hard on one side like me,
and the knot loses its balance.
You get the perfect shape
when both sides
are pulled equally like this.
- Oh, my.
- How pretty.
Good job today.
The way you explained the knot
was brilliant.
The crowd loved it too.
You look happy.
The boycott is over,
and Da-reum is back.
Your gamble paid off.
Chan.
I want to be
more honest with you now.
The truth is...
I'd rather not hear it.
Come to think of it
everything you kept from me
was something
that would break my heart.
So I will
pass on this one too.
Chan.
Welcome back.
It must've been hard for you.
I'm okay.
It must've been tough for you too.
I was a bit overwhelmed.
It felt terrible
that I couldn't protect you.
You did.
You even did that interview for me.
Thanks for seeing it that way.
What about your work?
Is everything okay?
You mean, the movie?
I wasn't let go.
Thank goodness.
Dealing with bad press and haters
isn't new to me.
I'm used to it.
Now that everything's out in the open
let's stop hiding.
I'm sorry?
Fan or friends, or whatever we are
I just want you to stay by my side.
You mean
a lot to me.
That sounds awfully
much like the past tense.
No, you still mean a lot to me.
- But...
- It's fine
even if someone else
means more to you.
I'm content...
as long as you're smiling.
Just stay by my side.
I want to start dating you
Da-reum.
I think I still see you
more as an idol
rather than a romantic partner.
INCOMING CALL: HA-GI
TRENDS WAIT FOR NO ONE
SE: ON
- Thank you.
- Thank you, we're SE: ON.
Thank you. Have a good day!
Hello, we're celebrating the opening
with a special event.
These are the brands that recently
ended exclusive contracts with us.
And here's the lineup
of SE: ON's newest brands.
Comparing the two...
CONTACT WITH SE CORPORATION
They're too...
As you can see,
the majority of our former partners
went straight to SE.
See? They swept them all up.
There definitely is a spy among us.
We have to root them out.
How else can you explain this?
Our priority right now
isn't pointing fingers.
It's defending our number one spot
in this business.
SE is going to push harder
and if we stay on the defensive,
they'll take over.
From here on out,
we'll go on the offensive.
Han.
Han?
It's the hottest name
in the fashion industry right now.
But...
Mr. Kang.
HAN is the most sought-after brand
in the Paris fashion scene.
Hold on. Is HAN the brand
SE is trying to partner with?
This is insane.
The only way
to turn this crisis around is
if we snatch HAN first.
We'll be setting up
a special task force.
Anyone's welcome to join.
That's going to be tough.
POP-UP EVENT PERFORMANCE REPORT
I've forwarded the access logs
and CCTV screenshots to your email.
Holy cow.
This is a massive scoop.
- I heard from the security room...
- Shush.
- Come.
- What?
- Is that Hye-soo?
- Yes.
Is she the one?
Ms. Seo.
You know that personal email usage
is prohibited at work, right?
- Yes, sir.
- Why'd you break security protocol?
I can't quite remember...
Why are you asking me this?
Oh, that's...
Don't tell me
you're accusing me of being the spy.
I swear it's not me.
Me, a spy?
That's absolutely ridiculous!
Spy or not, the dating scandal photos
certainly look like your doing.
This is for you.
I'm sorry.
What...
Mr. Kang, could you
check this for me?
You flat-out rejected
my feelings for you.
- What?
- I don't need it.
Then, buy me one.
Then I saw you
meeting privately with Da-reum.
It made me so mad.
Some reporter handed me
a business card.
- I had no idea it'd get this big.
- Ms. Seo.
Are you aware of how much
this has cost the company?
I'm so sorry.
CEO KANG HA-GI
You'll be disciplined
according to company policy.
And...
I suggest
you reflect on who truly deserves
your apology.
- Goodness.
- Good grief.
- Oh, my. Thank you.
- I'm more grateful.
I caught her thanks to your tip-off.
I'm basically
a walking security camera, you know.
Ms. Seo isn't the spy, though.
She just leaked the photos.
Oh, really?
Then, who is the real spy?
Regardless, thank you for your help.
Mr. Kang, I'll keep an eye out.
Why, that little...
I'm here to deliver fried chicken,
not take out the trash.
Seriously, where on earth is Roy?
QUICK DELIVERY
DRIVE SAFELY
Jeez. Watch where you're going!
Are you okay?
Wait, this voice...
Are you hurt?
Roy?
Oh, this is killing me. My back...
Goodness, my hip.
You're not even showing your face.
Are you trying to pull a hit-and-run?
A hit-and-run?
No, it's nothing like that.
Then take off that helmet
and apologize properly.
Take it off.
Come on. Please take it off.
I'm sorry. I was careless.
I apologize.
Here.
What? Oh, thanks.
Are you badly hurt?
Shall we go to the ER?
No, I'm fine.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- You can let go now.
- Right.
The brand HAN is really fascinating.
The Creative Director's identity is
under wraps.
All they have on social media is
their brand account.
I think that's what piques
everyone's curiosity.
That's enough for now.
Let's go eat. I'm starving.
- Good idea.
- Yes, let's eat.
Do you see this, everyone?
What does it look like?
I have the corporate credit card
in my hands.
- What do you want to eat?
- Budae-jjigae.
- Budae-jjigae? Let's go eat, then.
- Great.
Let's go. Let's go downstairs.
- Budae-jjigae.
- What else?
Spicy stir-fried webfoot octopus.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Gosh...
- Da-reum, you coming?
- Yes. I am.
She's an outcast.
She brought it on herself.
Ms. Seo.
Can I have a word?
Okay.
What was that?
Are they having a fight?
Ms. Seo.
What do you want?
What are you doing?
Are you going to beat me up?
No, wait, sorry. I'm really sorry.
Don't you have anything to say to me?
I'm sorry.
I really am.
I must've lost my mind.
Thanks to you, I ended up
submitting a written apology
and becoming an outcast.
I know I deserve
what I'm going through.
I'm having such a hard time
that I just want to quit.
I know.
Been there, done that.
If we don't make up,
things won't get better for you.
So what?
Are you going to be the bigger person
and forgive me or something?
Not yet.
But
I will hold out a helping hand.
If you actually feel bad
will you help me?
What?
How can I help you?
The HAN TFT proposal.
It's way too hard for me.
You've written loads of proposals.
Let's work on it together.
Together?
Yes.
Sure. Whatever.
Welcome.
Take your time to look around.
- Can you take a look?
- Okay.
Who's the director in charge
of this store?
Oh, that would be
our Director Lee Chan.
- I'll take this.
- Okay.
You can pay over there.
Let's meet up.
Stop avoiding me.
Are you Lee Chan?
Han Jeong-yeon?
- Let's talk another time.
- Okay.
It really is you.
When did you get to Korea?
Just a few days ago.
Has it been 15 years
since we last met?
You never called once.
Did you miss me?
I remember the old days.
They were the good times.
You and I used to listen
to music at school.
Do you remember?
We promised to go to a jazz bar
for some live music and whiskey
when you turned 20.
You weren't there when I turned 20.
I'm sorry about that.
But I missed you guys, though.
"You guys"?
You and Ha-gi.
Is he well?
You two were inseparable.
You haven't changed at all.
- How so?
- How you make me uncomfortable.
I thought becoming a celebrity
would've made you cool.
You haven't changed either.
I'm staying at the boutique hotel
across the road.
See you again soon.
You're incredibly good with a knife.
I used to go by the nickname
"Seocho's Knife-man."
The stench of blood back then...
"Knife-man"?
That's in the past.
Now I'm everyone's punching bag.
Was he disowned for having a record?
So what's your ideal type, Mi-mi?
My ideal type?
I like competent and capable men
who are good kissers.
That's a very clear answer.
That's me.
- I need to go to the ladies' room.
- Sure.
My heart's racing.
She wants to kiss already?
That's way too fast.
He looks incompetent.
I bet he's a lousy kisser.
Okay. Then what?
You don't have a knife.
How about we go
with kidnap and confinement?
Murder is too much.
Jeez. That's tricky.
Something urgent came up.
I have to dash.
Mi-mi!
Hold on, Mi-mi.
Why is he following me?
Now I'm scared.
What got into her? Mi-mi.
Darn it.
- I need help.
- With what?
Someone's chasing me.
My stomach hurts.
You forgot your coat.
ATTORNEY KIM MIN-WOO
TRUE
I don't know what you mistook me for,
but I really am an attorney.
You know the state my body's in.
What thug would have tech neck,
rounded shoulders, or a slipped disc?
Why didn't you say so from the start?
You never asked.
It's not a good look
to brag about your job
when no one asked.
Does this look right?
I wish we could add
a little something.
Can you excuse me?
Ms. Seo.
This is my initial draft.
How does it look?
Oh, well...
Page one makes the first impression,
and this looks too ordinary.
It's always good
to put the conclusion first.
In that case...
This part...
You two are working hard together.
- Do this first.
- Okay.
Then this.
- Three, one, two?
- Yes.
Okay. Got it.
Let's go home, everyone.
- Marketing Team.
- Yes?
Look at the time.
Why are you still here?
I still have work to do.
You've got the gist of it.
You just need to fix the details.
Finish it up tomorrow.
Rest is crucial for work.
- Go on home.
- Can you review my proposal, too?
- Go home.
- What? It's that perfect?
You can't finish this today.
Do it over tomorrow.
Okay, everyone. Pack up and go home.
- Go home.
- But...
- Bye.
- See you.
- Let's all go home.
- Go home.
- Okay.
- Go on home.
- Good job, guys.
- Let's go.
Finish it tomorrow.
You can't really cook, can you?
Well...
I guess so.
- I can't...
- I can't cook many things
but I make a mean pasta.
Do you?
All you have to do is
heat the bottled sauce
and add the pasta.
Ms. Da-reum.
Shall we swap tasks?
Why?
I'm really bad with knives.
What? Step aside, then.
I'll take over.
It's good.
- You're great at cooking pasta.
- Right? I told you so.
Eat at my place next time.
At your place?
The thing I'm second best at cooking
is tteokbokki.
We should have that next time.
Okay, let's do that.
So...
You knew it was Ms. Seo.
Why didn't you say so?
I didn't want to suspect
for no good reason.
You could've gone to anyone else
for help with your proposal.
I told you once before.
I used to be an outcast.
Looking at Ms. Seo made me think
about how tormented she must feel.
And also so lonely.
That's what came to my mind first.
I didn't want to see her...
go through what I did.
Ms. Da-reum.
Despite being hurt yourself
you choose to console others.
That's what you did for me.
Actually...
I've lived my life
doing the opposite.
I did my best
not to get too close to anyone.
It's because
whenever I cherished someone...
they ended up leaving me.
It was easier...
to throw myself into my work.
You managed
to break through that wall
to get to me.
Do you remember this wine?
Yes, it's the bottle I gifted you.
The wine that helps
one's love come true.
It actually worked.
MISSED CALL: HA-GI
HA-GI: PLEASE PICK UP
APPELLO KANG HA-GI
CEO KANG'S LEADERSHIP
SHINES THROUGH SCANDAL
Why was it Ha-gi?
What do you mean?
You chose him.
Why Ha-gi and not me?
It was us first.
We met first.
We connected first.
Hey, catch.
Whenever you smiled
I thought I was the reason
you were smiling.
So why
did you choose Ha-gi in the end?
Tell me.
The look in your eyes.
It's the same as back then.
You always wanted to rescue me.
I felt grateful
but I also hated it.
Why?
Your pity.
You look at me
like I was unfortunate.
Ha-gi didn't.
He liked me...
for who and what I was.
I felt at ease around him.
I thought
if I were with someone I like
I'd be able to share
my feelings with him
by laughing, crying
whining, and even fighting.
But for some reason
I couldn't easily do that
with you.
Did something happen
between you and Ha-gi?
No.
I shouldn't have come. Take care.
Chan.
Do you need my help?
See if you can win Ha-gi's heart.
They never even called us back
but they met up with SE Corporation.
We lost out this time.
Darn it.
HAN DIDN'T CREATE A BRAND
BUT AN AESTHETIC
Shall we return to the hotel?
No, we have one more place to go.
CEO KANG HA-GI
Mr. Kang.
HAN's CEO is coming to visit Appello.
- What?
- HAN, the brand.
They're on their way.
- Are they here?
- Yes.
Meet HAN's CEO, Ms. Han Jeong-yeon.
It's a pleasure.
Welcome to Appello.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Kang Ha-gi.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPILOGUE
Now, the five-second countdown.
No, three seconds.
- Three, two, one.
So about that.
- The slides.
- Move the table here.
- That should work.
- Okay.
- That looks better.
- Right?
- Yes.
- I think it's too big.
They might as well broadcast
that they're dating.
Right? They say when a couple
starts dating at work
everyone knows about it,
even the water cooler.
WITNESS 1
Let's start the meeting.
- Okay.
ROMANTIC NIGHT VIEW SPOTS IN SEOUL
SEOUL NIGHT DATE IDEAS
WITNESS 2
WITNESS 3
STORAGE
Da-reum, Ms. Kim needs the sample
urgently. Have you found it?
What?
- Yes, I'm bringing it now.
- Okay.
Let's pretend we have no idea.
They're both clueless
when it comes to dating.
- You're excited.
- Why are you so happy?
It gives me butterflies.
Haven't you ever been
in a relationship?
Han Jeong-yeon?
She's Ha-gi's first love.
If you ever make my Da-reum cry...
The person who wrote that proposal...
Would you like to lead the project?
Why Ms. Da-reum of all people?
Whatever it may be
I want you to do
what your heart tells you to do.
Does my relationship
with Mr. Kang bother you?
- But I trust the person I'm dating.
- Do you?
What does that mean?
I want Ha-gi back.
Were you with her all this while?
Subtitles by Eunjin Erica Kim
and Jennifer Jean Lim
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs